quotemountain.com 2016-03-09

# Famous Quotes Quotations Sayings Proverbs - QuoteMountain Famous Quotes

This is the web site of **_QuoteMountain.com_**.  We can be reached via e-mail at [admin@quotemountain.com](mailto:admin@quotemountain.com).   For each visitor to our site, our Web server automatically recognizes only the visitor's domain information and not the e-mail address.  We collect this information for statistical purposes only.  E-mail addresses of those who notify others of site content, those who communicate with us via e-mail, or survey information and/or site registrations are collected. 

The information we collect is used to improve the content of our site, used to notify visitors of updates to our site, and is not shared with outside organizations for commercial purposes. 

If you do not want to receive e-mail from us in the future, please let us know by sending an e-mail to the above address.  If you supply us with your postal address on-line you will only receive the information for which you provided us your address.  Persons who supply us with their telephone numbers on-line will only receive telephone contact from us with information regarding orders they have placed on-line. 

From time to time, we may use customer information for new, unanticipated uses not previously disclosed in our privacy notice.  If our information practices change, we will update our Privacy Statement on our site and notify our registered users at the email address supplied.   If you are concerned about how your information is used, check our Privacy Statement periodically as it will contain the most current information. 

Upon request we provide site visitors with access to all information [including proprietary information] that we maintain about them.   Site users can access this information by e-mailing us at the above address.  Consumers can have this information corrected or updated by sending us an e-mail at the above address. 

With respect to security: We have appropriate security measures in place in our physical facilities to protect against the loss, misuse, or alteration of information that we have collected from you at our site. 

We allow third-party companies to serve ads and/or collect certain anonymous information when you visit our web site. These companies may use non-personally identifiable information (e.g., click stream information, browser type, time and date, subject of advertisements clicked or scrolled over) during your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services likely to be of greater interest to you. These companies typically use a cookie or third party web beacon to collect this information. To learn more about this behavioral advertising practice or to opt-out of this type of advertising, you can visit www.networkadvertising.org . 

We partner with ValueClick as well as other companies to serve ads and/or collect certain information when you visit our website. ValueClick may use cookies or web beacons to collect non-personally identifiable information during your visit to this website in order to help show advertisements on other websites likely to be more interesting to you. To learn more about this “behavioral advertising” practice or to opt-out of this use of your anonymous information, you can visit http://www.valueclickmedia.com/member_privacy.shtml 

If you feel that this site is not following its stated information policy, please contact us by email. 

Thank You, 

**_QuoteMountain.com Administration_**
